{"data":[{"question":"The group of scientists ___ full use of the time they could to do experiments.","a":"get, save","b":"made, spare","c":"were, have","d":"had, use","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past (express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past) \n- Make use of: to make full advantage of something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Mother came into the kitchen and asked how I was ___ on with the cooking.","a":"getting","b":"working","c":"trying","d":"doing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Get on: to deal with a job or situation or to make progress","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"___ your words and phrases carefully while writing a composition.","a":"Take up","b":"Take out","c":"Pick","d":"Pick on","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Pick:to choose someone or something from a group","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Sometimes Maggie ___ Jessica's place on her way to the market.","a":"called on","b":"dropped in","c":"called","d":"dropped by","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Drop by: to visit someone you know, usually without arranging a particular time","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The number of workers in the international industry ___ more than one hundred thousands.","a":"is added up to","b":"adds to","c":"adds up to","d":"add up to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Active voice\n- The expression the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"I ___ play the violin when I was young, but I don't now.","a":"was used to","b":"would","c":"got used to","d":"used to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Please ___ yourselves to the pizza.","a":"have","b":"make","c":"help","d":"take","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Help oneself: to take some of what you want, without asking permission - used especially when offering food to someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"This developing center ___ an area of 200 acres.","a":"takes","b":"includes","c":"holds","d":"covers","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Cover: to spread over an area","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"I would rather ___.","a":"surf the Internet than watching TV","b":"surfing the Internet than watching TV","c":"to surf the Internet than to watch TV","d":"surf the Internet than watch TV","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Would rather do sth rather do sth else: used to say that you would prefer to do or have something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"While in her college days she used to ___ curly hair.","a":"wear","b":"have","c":"grow","d":"keep","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Wear: to have your hair or beard in a particular style or shape","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}